>> Brian Holt: 我接下来要做的就是希望从 ESLint 迁移此内容
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: The next thing I want to do
here is I want to migrate this from ESLint
到 TSLint。
to TSLint.
现在，让我们谈谈 TSLint的第二个问题。
Now, let's chat a second about TSLint.
他们计划最终除掉 TSLint 并把所有人都转移到 ESLint
They plan to eventually get rid of
TSLint and move everyone on to ESLint,
TypeScript 和 ESLint 正常用户，对吗 ?
both TypeScript and
ESLint normal users, right?
为什么我今天要教你 TSLint 呢
So why am I teaching you TSLint today?
因为他们还在移民的过程中
Because getting, they're still
in the process of migrating and
就会有一阵子了
it's going to take like a while.
我估计要一年多
I'm going to guess over a year for
最终让所有人从 TSlint 到 ESlint
them to finally get everyone
from TSlint on to ESlint.
因此， ESlint 还没有为 TypeScript 用户准备好。
And so ESlint is just not ready for
TypeScript users yet.
这就是为什么我现在要给你展示一下 TTS 。
So that's why I'm going to
show you TSlint right now.
因为现在如果我要启动一个全新的项目
Is because right now,
if I'm starting a brand new project,
我还是要用 TSlint 后来迁移到 ESlint，
I'm still going to use TSlint
then migrate later to ESlint,
因为在使用 TypeScript 时， TSlint 比 ESlint 更好。
because TSlint is just better at
working with TypeScript than ESlint is.
所以我们先去做吧
So let's go ahead and get that done.
所以我们要做， >> Brian Holt: 也许吧。
So we're gonna do,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Maybe.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 我们会说
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're gonna say pm,
卸载 eslint babel-eslint
uninstall eslint babel-eslint
eslint-config-prettier。
eslint-config-prettier.
>> Brian Holt: eslint-plugin-import。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: eslint-plugin-import.
>> Brian Holt: eslint plugin-jsx-a11y。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: eslint plugin-jsx-a11y.
还有埃斯皮林的反应
And eslint plugin-react.
还有埃斯皮林 - plug-in -hook-hook。
And eslint-plugin-react-hooks.
你能在这里做些什么
Now, what you could do here is
you could leave some of these and
把他们都夺走了而且他们都有
take away other of them, and
kind of have both of them.
Cuz ESlint 了解 TypeScript，
Cuz ESlint does understand TypeScript,
它还没有太多的 TypeScript 特定规则。
it just doesn't have very many
TypeScript specific rules yet.
现在我要给你演示如何把 ESlint 完全取出来
For now, I'm just gonna show you how
to take the ESlint out totally, and
使用 TTSlint 重新实施该工具。
reimplement it with TSlint.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，换句话说，我们将把所有
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so in other words,
we're going to take all of our
ESlint 的东西，我们要用 TSlint 的东西来代替它。
ESlint stuff out and we're going
to replace it with TSlint stuff.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，我们会说 ESlint 安装，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
we're going to say ESlint install,
sorry， blah， eslint， npm install -D tslint
sorry, blah, eslint, npm install -D tslint
tslint -反应 tslint-config-prettier。
tslint-react tslint-config-prettier.
>> Brian Holt: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay.
请在此处删除您的 eslint 配置文档。
Go ahead and
delete your eslint config doc here.
所以我要删除这个把它移到垃圾里
So I'm gonna delete that,
move it to trash.
然后我要在这里做一个新的文件。
And then I'm going to
make a new file here.
好吧我们先换个方法吧
Well, let's go ahead and
change this first.
转至 package.json。
Go to package.json.
并将 lint 更改为 tslint -project。
And change lint to be tslint --project.
>> Brian Holt: 所以这个 --project 意味着，哎，有一个 sconfig，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this --project means,
hey, there's a tsconfig,
从 tsconfig 中读取所有内容，从 TypeScript 获取。
read everything from the tsconfig,
which it's getting from TypeScript.
好了现在做个新文件
Okay, now make a new file.
一旦你把它变成了茨林特 -工程
Once you've gotten this lint one
changed to tslint --project.
新文件我们会叫它 tslint.json
New file, and
we're gonna call it tslint.json.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，我们要做的
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and we're going to do
扩展tslint:推荐，
extends tslint:recommended,
tslint - 反应，和
tslint-react, and
tslint - config-prettier。
tslint-config-prettier.
同样地，这两者的顺序并不重要，
So again, it doesn't matter
that the order of these two,
只会使配置更漂亮的情况更糟。
it just matters that
the config-prettier is last.
因为这样做才会让那些漂亮的东西都被处理掉了
Because all this does is turn off things
that prettier's already taken care of.
> > Brian Holt: 然后我们要关闭一些规则，因为
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we're gonna
turn off a bunch of rules, because
如果您不关闭这些规则中的某些规则，那么建议使用 tslint 。
tslint recommended is really annoying if
you don't turn off some of these rules.
所以下令进口
So ordered imports.
这就是你喜欢按字母表进口的地方
This is one where you have to
like alphabetize imports, and
我不是那种人
I am just not into that.
对象排序，让我们看到对象文字键排序。
Object sort,
let's see object literal key sort.
>> Brian Holt: 对象文字。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Object literal.
>> Brian Holt: 排序键，即一个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Sort keys, that's one.
这件事也是一样
This one, same thing.
它迫使您，如果您创建对象，那么必须将其中的所有键按字母顺序排列。
It forces you, if you make an object, you
have to alphabetize all of the keys in it.
不我为什么要那样做对吗
And no,
why would I ever wanna do that, right?
那么假的把那个关了
So false, turn that off.
没有控制台，我们正在某些地方使用控制台，因此关闭它。
No console, cuz we're using console
in some places, so turn that off.
>> Brian Holt: jsx-no-lambda 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: jsx-no-lambda.
这显然与钩子不起作用， [LAUGH]
This obviously would not work with hooks,
[LAUGH] so
你也可以把那个关掉
you can turn that one off as well.
>> Brian Holt: 成员排序，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And member ordering,
你要把事情按字母顺序排列
that's another thing where you
have to alphabetize things.
正如你所看到的，你可能会在这里捕捉一个主题。
And as you can see,
you might be catching a theme here.
我不想把任何东西都按字母
I don't want to alphabetize anything.
这只对我没有任何意义
That one just doesn't
make any sense to me.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，这应该让我们从茨林特开始。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
that should get us started with tslint.
下一件你想做的就是你想过来
The next thing that you probably wanna do,
is you wanna come over here and
您要搜索 tslint 以获取 VSCode 的扩展。
you wanna search for tslint for
an extension for VSCode.
显然也没有得到不推荐的
And obviously don't get
the deprecated one,
把微软做的那个装到这个
get the one that's made by
Microsoft here and install that.
这将使您能够直接在编辑器中看到所有这些 lint 错误。
And this will allow you to see all these
lint errors directly in your editor.